Łukasz Langer

Software Engineer

Independent and diligent developer with two years of experience in the IT industry. Known for my ability to swiftly adapt to changes and tackle complex challenges. Committed to ongoing growth and skill enhancement, I eagerly embrace new challenges.



+48 515 686 685



lukaszlanger1998@gmail.com

Experience

Diebold Nixdorf (Katowice)

Full-Stack Software Engineer November 2021 – August 2023

- Work in the scrum team on the development of the company's cross-platform, flagship application
- Software bug fixes and support
- Creating technical documentation
- Active cooperation with many foreign language teams

Subrest Daniel Piekarski (Katowice)

Customer service employee and IT technician May 2018 – September 2022

- Taking care of cyber security of devices and administration of operating systems
- Managing and scheduling my and other employees' responsibilities
- Working with customer service

JBS Serwis (Bytom)

IT technician April 2017 – May 2017

Computer hardware and software repair

iOutlet (Plymouth, UK)

*IT technician*April 2016 – May 2016

- Repair of Apple mobile devices
- iPhone and iPad fault diagnosis



Education

WSB Merito University in Chorzów

Master's degree in computer science with specialization *Python Developer*

Silesian University of Technology

Faculty of Materials Engineering

Engineering studies in the field of industrial computer science with a specialization in *Computer programming*.

Rector's scholarship for the third year

Languages

English **B2**Polish **C2**

Skills

C# (WPF, ASP.NET, .NET Core, MVC)
Entity Framework | Angular | TypeScript
Ionic Framework | Python | SQL (MySQL)
REST | HTML5/CSS | Git | Docker | Jenkins
Jira | Bitbucket | Confluence | Scrum